{
    "subject": "resource/Tribalistas",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedMusicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Timbalada",
    "human_readable": "Tribalistas is associated with Timbalada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9194293022155762,
            "question": "Which Brazilian music genre is often linked to Tribalistas and Timbalada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9092631340026855,
            "question": "Are Tribalistas and Timbalada known for collaborating musically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8276320099830627,
            "question": "What is the cultural significance of both Tribalistas and Timbalada in Brazil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7887458801269531,
            "question": "How do Tribalistas and Timbalada influence contemporary Brazilian music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.786561906337738,
            "question": "Can you describe the overall impact of Tribalistas and Timbalada on the Brazilian music scene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7727064490318298,
            "question": "Are there any other music groups that have a similar sound to Tribalistas or Timbalada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.76509028673172,
            "question": "What are some key characteristics that define the music of both Tribalistas and Timbalada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.761113703250885,
            "question": "What type of musical production style might both Tribalistas and Timbalada share?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7599514722824097,
            "question": "Can you name any popular songs by either Tribalistas or Timbalada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5428388118743896,
            "question": "What musical group is associated with Timbalada?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tribalistas is associated with Timbalada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8601_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any popular songs by either Tribalistas or Timbalada?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8601_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of musical production style might both Tribalistas and Timbalada share?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8601_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key characteristics that define the music of both Tribalistas and Timbalada?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8601_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8601_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Carlinhos Brown, who is part of the musical supergroup Tribalistas, was also a member of Timbalada. This information supports the statement that Tribalistas is associated with Timbalada."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}